仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  冰蓝   洗七里   MsFool
翻译:  吃货丁小七   小泡椒
校对:  猛男俱乐部赛太公
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第六集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
一键收藏网盘资源生活大爆炸 吸血鬼日记
西部世界 谍网 超女
美剧资源应有尽有
扫码即刻关注
Zimuzu特别推荐
马上关注微信人人美剧（rrmjapp）
好啊  宝贝弟弟
Hey, baby brother!
我们别侮辱彼此了  你要多少钱
Let's not insult us both. How much do you need?
妈妈帮我先付了这个月的汽车保险
Mom paid my car insurance this month,
我跟她说我今天会有钱...
and I told her I'd have it today --
-告诉我数字就好  -120元
- The number, the number. - $120.
外公帮我在他的乡村俱乐部找了份工作
Grandpa got me a job at his country club,
我在打扫卫生赚小费
and I've been cleaning up in tips.
我还喜欢这些人的霸气说话方式
I also like the way those guys talk.
原来有专门对挪威人的种族蔑称呢
There's actually an ethnic slur for Norwegians.
叫冰[哔]
It's ice ers.
儿子  他们取消来看房
Hey, buddy, they canceled my showing,
我可以开车载你去上班了
so I can drive you to work.
看起来不错啊  是什么
That looks good. What is it?
乡村俱乐部的热月龙虾
Lobster Thermidor from the country club.
冰箱里还有"樱桃盛宴"甜点
There's also cherries jubilee in the fridge.
瞧瞧我们  吃得像是50年代的富人一样
Look at us eating like rich people in the '50s.
好啊  妈妈  祝你今天工作顺利
Hey, Mom! Have a good day at work.
我已经上完班了  都三点半了
Uh, I already did that. It's 3:30.
你怎么能现在才刚醒
How are you just waking up?
我把闹钟定在了中午  我肯定是睡过去了
I set my alarm for noon. I must have slept through it.
我工作得很晚  为一家新的酒吧宣传
I was working late promoting a new club.
对了  这是汽车保险的钱
Oh, by the way, here is the insurance money.
-谢谢  -里面有很多一元纸币啊
- Thank you. - A lot of singles in there.
你到底在这个酒吧做什么"工作"
What exactly do you do at this club?
对
Oh, right.
因为我是脱衣舞女  艾丽克斯
'Cause I'm a stripper, Alex.
天啊  你们真觉得我是个脱衣舞女吗
Oh, my God, do you really think I'm a stripper?
-不觉得  -不觉得
- No. - No.
好了  我走了
Okay, well, I'm off.
我要去社区大学
I'm signing up for some business classes
报名参加一些商务课
at community college.
商务课啊
Business class, huh?
看来有人受到了影响啊
Sounds like somebody's been influenced
因为她和一个行业巨头
by living under the same roof
住在同一个屋檐下
with a certain captain of industry.
谢谢你  亲爱的  但要不是
Thank you, honey, but none of my success
有你照顾家并支持我  我也不可能成功
would have been possible without your support as a homemaker.
亲爱的  你突然对商业感兴趣了
Sweetheart, while I'm very flattered
我真是觉得很荣幸
by your sudden interest in business,
但你还是别再上课了  而是找份工作吧
how about instead of another class, you get a job?
把手弄脏[亲自干活]吧
Get your hands a little dirty, huh?
她可以用手抓抓头发
She could run her hands through her hair.
-那就脏了  -我已经预注册了
- That would do it. - I've already pre-registered.
我还报名了今晚的签售会
Also, I signed us up for that book signing tonight.
你还来吗
You still in?
绝对的
Absolutely.
我的书就在这
Got my book right here.
-想把这本书弄成你看过的样子吗  -外行
- Trying to make it look like you read it? - Amateur.
我的工作没有职称
So, I don't really have a job title
也没有固定的工作地点
or even a set place to work,
所以我就转来转去
so I kind of just float around
确保所有人得到了需要的东西
and make sure everyone has what they need.
四点了  法官大人
4:00, Your Honor.
别忘了吃药
Don't forget to take your medicine.
这都是有权有势的人
Well, all these powerful guys.
你可以在这里积累永恒的人脉
You can make connections here that'll last forever.
也不行
Not really.
这里经常有人去世
We have a lot of turnover here.
从四月以来  外面就一直在降半旗
That flag outside has been at half-mast since April.
所以才有这个
That's why we have these.
今晚  准会员鸡尾酒派对
这是怎么回事
Oh. How's that work?
你找个会员为你担保
You find a member to sponsor you,
过来跟委员会喝点酒
come have some drinks with the committee,
他们会投票选出一些新会员
and they vote a few people in.
跟我曾加入的秘密拉拉队组织程序差不多
Similar process to a secret cheer society I was in.
骷髅头和拉拉队绒球
Skull and Pom-Poms.
我已经泄露太多了
I've said too much already.
你想加入吗
Are you thinking of joining?
我的两个合作伙伴都在俱乐部里
Both my partners are in clubs.
他们招徕了许多生意
They've drummed up a lot of business.
也许我...
Maybe I --
那是杰  也许他可以
Hey, there's Jay. Maybe he can --
杰  杰
Jay. Jay!
杰杰杰
Jay, Jay, Jay!
快走
Go, go, go!
杰  等等
Jay, wait up!
我觉得有人在叫你
I think someone's calling for you.
我什么都没听见  这车怎么了
I didn't hear anything. What's wrong with this cart?
-你踩了刹车吗  快啊  -你的钉鞋
- You got the brakes on? Go! - Ow! Your spikes.
跑太快有点抽筋了
Hey, hey, hey! Cramps.
卢克和我刚一起吃了一块威灵顿牛排
Luke and I just split a Beef Wellington
和卡西诺烧蛤
and clams casino.
我想知道你能否为我担保
Um, I'm wondering if you'd, uh, sponsor me
让我参加今晚的新会员派对
for the new-members thing tonight.
天啊  我很乐意  但他们有规定
Gee, I'd like to, but they got rules
亲戚不能为新会员担保  所以
about relatives sponsoring new members, so --
他们没有  我就这样做了
No, they don't. I just did it.
天啊  他们肯定是改规定了
Gee, they must have changed that.
真棒  今晚见  我该几点来
Oh, great, I'll see you tonight. What time should I be here?
我想大概九点半开始吧
Oh, I think it starts about 9:30.
不  那时候就结束了  七点开始
No, it'll be over by then. It starts at 7:00.
他们肯定也改时间了
They must have changed that, too.
谢谢你  杰  七点见
Thanks, Jay. See you at 7:00.
等等  那是克莱尔的丈夫对吧
Wait, that was Claire's husband, right?
是的  安德斯  你这个愚蠢的冰[哔]
Yes, it was, Anders, you stupid ice
六个月来  我从来没机会独处一晚
I haven't had one night to myself in six months,
但今晚  曼尼要去参加派对
but tonight, Manny's going to a party.
如果我能让乔累到睡觉
And if I can get Joe tired enough to go to sleep,
我就终于可以放松  洗个长长的舒服澡了
I can finally relax and take a long, nice bath.
我还有一个能浮起来的酒杯
I even have a wine glass that floats.
就算我睡着了  也不会发生糟糕的事
In case I fall asleep, nothing bad can happen.
好了  小驯鹿
Ohh. Okay, little reindeer,
我们还没到北极呢
we didn't get to the North Pole yet.
我不想玩这个游戏了
I'm tired of this game.
我们得把这食物送给圣诞老人
Well, we need to take this food to Santa Claus.
如果不送  他就会饿死
If not, he's gonna starve to death.
我该穿哪件参加派对
Which shirt for the party --
淡黄色还是黄水仙色
the canary or the daffodil?
别又来了
We're not doing this again.
我刚帮你决定了背心是选人字呢还是粗花呢
I just did the herringbone or the tweed for your vest.
随便选一件然后去吧
Just pick one and go.
好吧  这件需要熨烫
Okay. Oh, well, this needs ironing.
好吧  上车
Okay, jump on.
驯鹿鲁道夫  去洗衣房
Rudolph, to the laundry room!
我知道这只是社区剧场
I know it's just community theater,
但是首映夜真是令人激动啊
but aren't opening nights so exciting?
是啊  社会精英
Yes, the cream of society
-穿上最好看的人字拖  -米奇尔
- decked out in their finest flip-flops. - Mitchell.
天啊  我真不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe it.
高中后我就没见过你了
I haven't seen you since high school!
是的  好多年了对吧  泰咪
Uh, yes, it's been years, huh, uh, T-T-Tammy.
如果你想
Hey, let me know
再跟我去看台下面"滚"几圈  告诉我一声
if you want to roll around under the bleachers again, doll.
好奇怪  感觉我应该能记住她这样的啊
That's weird -- I feel like I would've remembered her.
-她为什么要贴着名牌啊  -我不知道
- Why was she wearing a name tag? - I don't know.
是你啊
Oh, there he is!
还记得我们玩乐队的时候
Remember that time in band
你把笛子掉进水沟那次吗
when you dropped your flute in the gutter?
抱歉  我从来没吹过长笛之类的
I'm sorry -- I never played the flute or anything --
老水沟吹笛手
Ha! Old gutter flute.
好吧  这到底怎么回事
Okay, what is going on?
为什么所有人都在跟我说话
Why is everyone talking to me?
-我猜他们只是表达善意  -小卡  天啊
- I think they're just being friendly. - Cam, oh, my God.
这是那种互动式剧院吗
Is -- is this one of those interactive theater experiences?
你是说那种观众参与其中的
Oh, do you mean where the audience participates
故意模糊表演者
and the line between performer and spectator
和观众之间的界限的表演吗
is delightfully blurred?
米奇尔  这是一个高中同学会
Mitchell, we're at a high-school reunion!
别装了  好吗  你已经骗到我了
Stop pretending, all right? You tricked me.
-我没有  -你老是骗我
- I did not. - You always trick me.
我们每次出门
Every time we leave the house,
都像是在跟诈欺师斗智斗勇
it's like a game of Three-card Monte.
互动式剧院很有意思
Interactive theater is fun.
没意思  一点意思都没有
It's not fun. It's never fun.
这是人类在和平时期所能遇到的
It's the worst thing that can happen to human
最糟糕的事
during peace time.
好吧  米奇尔
Okay, you know what, Mitchell?
拜托  我是管理层的人
Please, I'm on the board,
别人的亲密爱人都开心出席
and I couldn't not bring my husband
我怎么能不把我丈夫
while everyone else's significant other
带来呢
is happy to be here.
所以这是互动剧院吗
It's interactive?
你个贱逼
You son of a bitch.
那句可以上你们的宣传海报
There's a quote for your poster.
-前门开了  -不是吧
- Front door open. - Ay, no!
拜托  是谁  是谁
Please. Who?! Who?!
你到底还在这里干什么
Ay, what the hell are you doing here?
我刚经历了人生中最尴尬的事
I had the most humiliating experience of my entire life.
我可能永远都不要走出这个家了
I may never leave this house again.
好了  你只是累了
Okay, you're just tired.
我给你倒杯咖啡  你就可以再战了
I'm gonna make you an espresso, and you go back.
不  我不能再去了
No, I can't go back there.
你又因为调节灯光惹麻烦了吗
Did you get in trouble again for adjusting the lighting?
你还年轻
You're still young.
光线亮一点没关系
You can take a bright bulb.
我本来在逗艾娃·莫里斯开心
I was flirting with Ava Morris,
结果小腿胫骨狠狠地撞上了
and I walked into a coffee table
一张咖啡桌
and hit my shin really hard
然后在所有人面前哭出来了
and started crying in front of everyone.
已经够惨了吧  然后我发现
Bad enough -- but then I noticed
我不小心洒了点饮料在裤裆处
I spilled my drink on my crotch area,
那画面被人看见我就玩完了
creating a very incriminating stain.
所以我冲去洗手间想拿毛巾擦干
I ran to the bathroom and started drying it with a towel,
结果门开了
but the door swung open,
然后全班同学都看到了
and I was viewed by my classmates
我擦自己"腹部下方"的样子
vigorously attending to my groin.
我刚有提到艾娃祖母穿着比基尼滑水的照片
Oh, and did I mention the picture of Ava's grandmother
当时刚好挂在我眼前的方位吗
water skiing in a bikini that was directly in my eyeline?
这种事谁都碰到过
That happens to everyone sometimes.
只要你喝点咖啡就没...
You're gonna be fine once you drink --
不
Ay, no!
妈妈  妈妈  妈妈
Hi, Mama! Hi, Mama! Hi, Mama!
在工作场所  我们女性被要求
In the workplace, we women have been told
谦让  容忍  无视
to suppress it, contain it, ignore it.
你知道我怎么说吗
Well, you know what I say?
-抓住机会  -抓住机会
- Grab it! - Grab it.
艾丽克斯不是我们家最擅长表达的孩子
Alex is not my most expressive child,
但当她去上了一门商科课程
but when she enrolled in a business class
然后听了一系列名为
and then signed up for a lecture series
"直面女总裁"的讲座之后
called "Meet the She-E-O,"
我就很清楚地了解她的意思了
it was pretty clear to me what she was trying to say --
"我崇拜你  妈妈"
"I admire you, Mom."
-所以你怎么看  -安静
- So, what do you think? - Quiet.
-我觉得...  -别说话
- I think -- - Stop talking.
我知道  这很不容易
I mean, sure, it was tough --
养大三个孩子  还要兼顾事业
raising three kids and running a business.
不过当我有机会成为女总裁时
But when the chance to be She-E-O arose,
我只有一个想法
I had only one thought.
抓住机会  抓住机会  抓住机会
Grab it. Grab it. Grab it. Grab it.
我懂了  我抓住机会了
I get it. I grabbed it.
你再这样我换座位了
I will move my seat.
一个母亲知道怎样读出孩子的潜台词
A mother knows how to read between the lines.
艾丽克斯嘴里说着"你这样让我很尴尬"
Alex's mouth may have said, "You're embarrassing me."
但心里一定在说"你激励了我"
But her heart was saying, "You're inspiring me."
"让我自己待着"
"Leave me alone."
"请给我指引"
"Show me the way."
"你还没说完吗"
"Are you still talking?"
"请永远这么牛逼"
"Never stop rocking."
好吧  第一个问题
Okay, first question.
前面这位
Ah, right up front.
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
你好  我是艾丽克斯
Hi, I'm Alex.
长期粉丝  但第一次抓住机会
Long-time reader, first-time grabber.
总之  我在加州理工读生化专业
Anyway, I'm a biochemistry major and CalTech,
但你的书让我对商科产生兴趣
but your book got me thinking about a business career.
所以我现在在考虑双专业
And now I'm considering double-majoring,
但这样是不是负担太重
but is that taking on a little too much?
艾丽克斯  看着我
Alex, look at me.
你能想到  就能抓到
If you can think it, you can grab it.
天哪
Aah! Oh, my God!
你是我的英雄  南希  谢谢
You're my hero, Nancy. Thank you.
下一位
Who's next?
-我有个...  -我就简单说一句
- I've got a -- - just a quick comment.
我也抚养了三个孩子
Um, I also raised three children,
同时是一间大公司的女总裁
and I am the She-E-O of a large company.
我得说
And I got to say,
看到你就像看我自己  南希
it's like looking a mirror, Nancy.
真棒  是哪间公司
That's great. What's the company?
普利切特衣橱及窗帘公司
Pritchett's Closets and Blinds.
你们卖橱柜和窗帘吗
You sell closets and blinds?
一般不是卖百叶窗和窗帘  或者橱柜和...
I could understand shutters and blinds or closets and...
我们公司生意很好  南希
We're good, Nancy.
我想说的是  在你书的第一页
What I wanted to talk about was how on page 1 of your book,
你为什么会说很难不把工作带回家做呢
you say you had hard time not bringing your work home.
那只是个玩笑
That was just a joke.
你应该记得  我的事业起始于我自己的车库
As you remember, my business was started in my garage.
所以你知道重要的不只是跟家人一起的时间
So, you know how it's not just family time that matters.
而是高质量的家人共处时光
It's quality family time.
我同意
I agree.
这就是我对孩子实施在家教育的原因
That's why I home-school all three of my children.
其实我们董事会的会议桌
The conference table in our boardroom
就在他们的游乐设施旁边
actually rests on their play structure.
我在说什么呢  站起来  孩子们
What am I saying? Stand up, kids?
仨个不同爸爸  是吗
So, three daddies?
你听上去像个疯子
You sound insane!
好啦
All right.
普里契特  那不是你的同性恋儿子么
Hey, Pritch, isn't that your gay son?
女婿
Son-in-law.
你的女婿也是同性恋吗
You've got a gay son-in-law, too?
我不要再随你们起舞了
I'm not doing this dance with you guys again.
我不知道自己在担心什么
I don't know what I was worried about.
我只需要让菲尔做自己就行
All I had to do was let Phil be Phil.
他不可能通过投票的
He'd never get past the vote.
幸运的是  即使是最高法院
Fortunately, clueless boobs are one group
也无法强迫我们让蠢蛋入会
the Supreme Court can't force us to let in.
跟我们说说你的事  菲尔
So, tell us about yourself, Phil.
事实上  我们有一些共同点
Well, uh, you and I have something in common, actually.
我们都是议员
We're both Congressmen.
继续说  菲尔
Go on, with that, Phil.
你在州议会
You're in the state congress,
而我曾参加过低年级翻筋斗大赛[议会]
and I was in the Junior Tumbling Congress.
我也参加过翻筋斗大赛
I was in Tumbling Congress.
你玩蹦床吗
You trampoline?
我一周有三晚都在玩蹦床
I'm on my tramp like three nights a week!
剩余的几晚  我都在陪我的娇妻
The rest of the time, I'm -- I'm with my wife.
我带着全现款且无额外条件的报价找到那卖家
So, I go back to the seller with an all-cash no-contingency offer
我的报价不仅够他还清房贷
that'd pay off both his mortgages
而且他的资本收益
and leave enough after capital gains
还足够付一间公寓的首付款
to put a down payment on a condo.
我给他一小时  否则我就撤回报价
I give him an hour or I'm pulling the offer.
我喜欢这故事  就像西部片一样
I love this story. It's like a western.
真是场噩梦
It was a nightmare.
翻筋斗往事  烂笑话  他们居然照单全收了
Tumbling stories, bad jokes, and they ate it up!
要我说他们只是客套一下
I'd say they were being polite,
但我曾亲眼看到其中两个狠人
but I've personally seen two of those guys
开车撞倒了行人时  减速都不减速呢
hit pedestrians and not even slow down!
不  真人真事  真人真事
No, true story! True story.
失陪一下
One second.
这些人赞爆了
These guys are great.
听着
Listen.
你还差一股劲把气氛炒到最热  而我在想
You need one more move to drive this home, and I'm thinking,
菲尔如何把派对炒热到前无古人后无来者
what does Phil bring to the party no else does?
魔术
Magic.
你确定吗  我有点生疏了
Are you sure? I'm a little rusty.
我看好你
My money's on you.
大秀一场  然后滚蛋
Go big, then go home.
-听上去像是你...  -大家注意下
- Sounded like you said -- - Hey, everybody!
菲尔要给你们表演几个魔术
Phil's gonna do a little magic trick for you.
好吧
Okay, uh...
这个魔术献给这里所有的律师
This one is for all of the lawyers in the room
因为你们可擅长将我们的钱...
because you're so good at making our money...
给变没了
disappear.
稍等
Oh, hold on.
莫里议员  别再提纳税了
Congressman Morley, enough with the taxes.
你也没见我们逼你
You don't see us making you pay...
付大钱[从鼻孔]
through the nose.
等等  大家别动  我能搞定
Okay, hold on. Nobody move, I got this!
我骗谁呢  我睡不着觉的
Who am I kidding? I can't fall asleep.
每声汽车警报  以及那窸窣的风声
Every car alarm, every whistle of the wind
听上去都像有人在嘲笑我
sounds like people laughing at me.
这些都是你的臆想
It's all in your imagination.
我只想付费电视上看看《极品老妈》
I just want to Netflix and Mom.
曼尼  你不明白
Manny, you don't understand.
一小时前  我放了一缸的完美的热水
An hour ago, I had made the perfect tub!
再次向你表示感谢  但没啥帮助
Yeah, thanks again for that, but it didn't help.
糖果  我爱糖果
Sugar! I love sugar!
好了  够了
Okay, that is it!
你小子不想去睡觉
You don't want to go to sleep!
而你小子不想去参加派对
And you don't want to go to the party!
-那我这就取消今晚的时光  -妈妈
- Then I'm canceling the nighttime! - Mom?
你听见了  已经到明天了
You heard me. It's tomorrow.
我们这就去学校  到车上等我
We're going to school. Wait for me in the car.
你好  杰
Hey, Jay.
如果你听到留言  求你快...
If you get this, please come --
现在没人能帮你了
No one can help you now!
看上去大家都来了
Yo, looks like everyone made it.
但弗拉德在哪
But where's Vlad?
那个拉脱维亚的交换生吗
The exchange student from Latvia?
我没见到他
I haven't seen him.
我真想再见见那个美男
I'd love to catch up with that dreamboat.
高中毕业后发生太多的事了
So much has happened since high school.
酗酒
Alcoholism.
我试图从酒瓶底寻找幸福
I tried to find happiness in the bottom of a bottle.
对人生苦痛惊天地泣鬼神的描述
A shattering depiction of human suffering.
但还不足以描述我的感受
But enough about how I felt.
我依旧记得我和弗拉德
I just keep remembering how Vlad and I
在高中共度的快乐时光
had the best time in high school.
对我们中某些人来说  却是最后的快乐时光
For some of us, that was the last best time.
越南战争
Vietnam.
这高中时代是发生在哪个年代啊
What time period was all this taking place?
完全说不通
It didn't make any sense.
我和弗拉德分手的那些事
The way things ended with me and Vlad,
至今令我心有余悸
it still haunts me.
很多事也都还令我心有余悸
A lot of things haunt me.
那是毕业舞会的夜晚
It was the night of the prom.
出车祸
Car accident.
路面上结满了冰
The roads were very icy.
-出车祸嘛  -不知道别瞎说
- Car accident. - You don't know.
透过迷雾  我看见了卡车的车头灯
Through the mist, I saw the truck's headlights.
当我醒来  医生告诉我我经历了一场惨烈的
When I came to, the doctor told me we'd been in a horrible
-车祸  -车祸
- car accident! - Car accident.
大姐你有没有搞错
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
米奇尔  这里是剧院  放尊重点
Mitchell, this is the theater. Have some respect.
你只需要乖乖坐着别出声
All you have to do is sit there and be quiet.
泰咪  你绝不会相信谁来了
Tammy, you are never gonna believe who's here.
-是谁  -弗拉德
- Who? - Vlad.
天啊  他在哪里
Oh, my God, where?
就在那
Out there.
就是他  他就是弗拉德
There he is. That's Vlad.
我发誓我不知道他们为啥选你
I swear I didn't know they were gonna pick you.
他们可能觉得你会比较逗
They probably assumed you were fun
因为你是和我一起的  他们太傻太天真
because you were with me. They didn't know.
弗拉德  快上台来
Vlad, come up here.
挪开你的乡下大屁股  我要走人了
Move your country ass. I'm -- I'm leaving.
不  不
No, no.
你就上台去拥抱一下泰咪
Just go up there, hug Tammy,
然后等着惊喜结局就好
and wait for the surprise ending.
我才不在乎什么惊喜结局
I don't care about the surprise ending!
你上去演弗拉德去
You go be Vlad.
我不能演弗拉德  因为我就是那个惊喜结局
I can't be Vlad because I am the surprise ending.
-什么  -那将是令观众掌声不断的表演
- What? - And it's a show-stopper.
我已经排练好几周了
I've been rehearsing for weeks.
你别这么自私了  快上台去吧
Now, just stop being selfish and get up there.
你就上去吧
Just do it!
我们都想快点完事走人
We all want to get out of here!
弗拉德
Vlad.
我也不知道是何时  用什么招
I didn't know how, I didn't know when,
但我知道此仇不报非君子
but I was gonna get him.
弗拉迪宝贝  亲爱的  你来了
Vladdie, sweetie, you're here.
你真的来了
Oh, you're really here.
自重
Not okay.
多圆满的结局啊
Oh, what a happy ending.
我也"圆满"了
I'll say.
行了行了
Okay, okay.
你的口香糖都跑我嘴里来了
That-That is your gum.
多棒的同学会啊
What a great reunion.
是啊  所有人都来了
Yeah, everybody made it.
几乎所有人
Almost everybody.
同学们好
Hello, students!
校工老乔
Janitor Joe!
或者我该说同学们永别了
Or should I say farewell?
突然间我有了复仇的灵感
All of a sudden, I knew how.
同学们  又见面了
Hello again, students.
或者我该说  永别了
Or should I say farewell?
此时不报  更待何时
And I knew when.
等等  大家都看到他的鬼魂了吗
Wait, wait, does-does anybody else see his ghost right now?
什么
What?
是啊  有谁能忘记
Yeah, who could forget
他鼓起勇气来参加我们25周年的同学会
how he courageously showed up to our 25th
然后死在我们所有人面前的情景
and then-and then died in front of all of us.
不  我现在刚要死
No, I'm about to die right now.
其实我还记得  他临死时
Mm-hmm, in fact, I-I remember his death
大概是这样的
went a little something like-like this.
我度过了漫长的一生
I've lived a long life.
米奇尔  你在干什么
Mitchell, what are you doing?
结交了那么多朋友
Many friends.
我美丽的妻子贝丝
Oh, my beautiful Bess.
甚至还去了华盛顿特区
Even took a trip to Washington, D.C.,
让我的照片跟议员大人合影
and had my picture made with the Congressman.
但当然我膝下无子
Never had any children, of course.
所以今晚来参加同学会对我如此重要
Which is why it was so important that I made it here tonight.
来见见你们所有人
To see each of you.
你们都是我的孩子
You are my children!
我想最后再留给你们这样一句诗
And I want to leave you with this one last thing.
-不要温和地  -不要温和地走进那个良夜
- Do not go gentle -- - Do not go gentle into that good night.
英国诗人狄兰·托马斯的代表作
要怒斥
Rage!
怒斥光明的消逝
Rage against the dying of the light!
我也感觉身体不太舒服
And I don't feel good either.
救场救得"好"
Yeah, good save.
扒到那个"抓住机会"女士的丑事了吗
Find anything on "Grab It" lady?
"南希·德克尔法律纠纷"  无结果
"Nancy Decker lawsuit" -- nope.
"南希·德克尔鼻子整形"  无结果
"Nancy Decker nose job" -- nope.
"南希·德克尔杀..."  有了
"Nancy Decker kills..." -- Oh!
"...在总裁喜剧之夜大杀四方"
"...at CEO comedy night."
你们好  我们来了
Hello, we're here.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
海莉  你还记得那天
Haley, you remember that day
你说无论什么时候我需要保姆
when you said that if I ever needed a nanny,
你都愿意帮我照看乔吗
you would love to take care of Joe?
-人给你  -不不
- Well, here you go. - No, no.
想留几年随便你
You can keep him for as long as you want.
谢了
Thank you.
不  那话听起来不像我说的
Uh, no, uh, that doesn't really sound like me,
再说我现在的工作是晚九朝五  再见
plus I have a 9-to-5 job now, so bye.
求你把我也带走吧
Please take me with you.
这是什么情况
What's going on?
妈妈疯了
Mama's crazy.
我才没疯
I am not crazy!
我不过是取消了这个夜晚
I just canceled the night.
曼尼  你给我解释一下吧
Manny, maybe you could help out here.
老妈发飙是因为乔不肯去睡觉
Mom's upset because Joe won't go to sleep
我又不肯回到某个派对上
and I won't go back to a party.
你不肯回到派对上  为什么
You won't go back to a party? Why?
我不幸遭遇了一连串尴尬事件
I suffered an unfortunate series of embarrassing incidents.
我只想喝点小酒泡个澡去睡觉
I just want a wine bath and to go to sleep.
听我说  曼尼
Listen up, Manny.
在经历了那个派对上发生的事以后
Of course you want to run away
也难怪你想逃跑
from whatever happened back that party.
任何人都会想逃
Anybody would.
但那样这些糗事就保证会跟着你到永远了
But that just guarantees that it sticks with you forever.
但如果你昂首阔步回到派对上
But if you march back in there
不以为耻反以为荣
and you own it,
你让那些乌合之众明白你比他们强
you let those people know that you're better than them,
你就会是传奇人物了
and you will be a legend.
-好  -没错
- Okay. - Yeah.
"好"
"Okay"?
你  躺沙发上睡觉去
You, get on the couch, go to sleep.
可我不困啊
But I'm not tired.
我才不管  5  4  3
Don't care. Five, four, three...
好吧  我去睡
Okay, I'm going!
-2  -"好吧  我去睡"
- Two... - "Okay, I'm going"?
我努力了好几个小时  而你上来就
I spend hours trying, and then you just come one --
我做的不过是不做他们的老妈
The only thing I did was not be their mother.
这其中的道理我也不懂  但出于某种原因
Look, I don't get it either, but for some reason...
孩子们都比较愿意听其他大人的话
the kids respond better to other adults.
是啊  但那太不公平了
Yeah, but that's not fair.
为人父母大部分时候都没有公平可言
Well, most of being a parent isn't fair.
现在艾丽克斯迷上了
Right now, Alex is obsessed
一个什么CEO商业女强人作家
with some CEO business woman author
她基本上就是个看起来老一点版本的我
who's basically an older-looking version of me.
顺带一提我和她同龄
We're the same age, by the way.
你知道艾丽克斯很崇拜你  对吧
You know that Alex look up to you, right?
从她对我说的话里还真听不出来
Not by anything she says, no.
他们从不说出口
Yeah, they never say it.
我猜他们认为
I guess they think
说出口会让父母有太多掌控权了
that they're giving the parents too much power.
他们像掉饼干渣一样用些小细节展示出来
They find little ways to express it.
当孩子妈就像当模特一样
Being a mom is like being a model.
得习惯舔着那一点饼干渣过日子
You have to learn how to live on crumbs.
宝贝你回来了
Hi, honey.
好吧
Right.
宝贝  我为我今晚的行为道歉
Honey, I'm so sorry about the way I was tonight.
没关系的
It's okay.
我还因此得到机会去后台见南希呢
I actually got to go backstage and meet Nancy.
她请我们几个去喝咖啡
She invited a few of us out for coffee.
挺好玩的
Oh, fun.
对  不  其实不好玩
Yeah, no, uh, not fun, actually.
她一直在那聊她自己
All she did was talk about herself.
好像她其实只是需要听众
It really just seemed like she wanted an audience.
当账单送过来的时候  你猜她没做什么
And when the check came, you know what she didn't do?
抓住它
Grab it.
对不起
Sorry.
乔在沙发上睡觉
Joe's sleeping in the couch.
他能待在这吗  好的  太感谢了
Can he stay here? Okay, thank you so much.
但今晚也不是完全没有收获
Well, I mean, the night wasn't a total waste.
她走了之后  我坐在那想
After she left, I sat there thinking,
"我为什么要选一门商务课"
"Why am I taking a business course anyway?"
世界那么大  我该去做点什么
I should go out in the world and do something.
所以我看到了咖啡馆里的招聘启示
So I saw a help-wanted sign in the coffee shop
然后得到了一份咖啡师的工作
and got a job as a barista.
真的吗
Really?
真的  明天开始
Yeah, I start tomorrow.
我很兴奋
I'm excited.
我刚还在想  为什么不出去
I just thought, why not get out there
把手弄脏[亲自干活]
and get my hands a little dirty, you know?
晚安
Good night.
桑拿在这
Sauna over here.
浴缸在那里
Hot tub that way.
传说单人淋浴隔间
Legend has it that the holes
里面的洞
in the individual shower partitions
是用来当雪茄架的
were cigar holders.
至少这是我们对外坚持的说法
At least that's the story we're sticking to.
也可以是性交用的寻欢洞
跟我来  伙计们
Follow me, folks.
来过这吗  杰
Ever been in here, Jay?
这里看上去是个
This looks like a good place
吃完甜点后  出场大汗的减肥好地方
to sweat out some Peach Melba.
你干了什么
What did you do?
我卡住了
I'm stuck.
我觉得门缝里卡了一条湿毛巾
I think there's a wet towel wedged underneath the door.
你能把它拉出来吗
Could you pull on it?
以后要整天这样了吗
Is this gonna happen all the time now?
我是不是得无时无刻照看你
Me babysitting you every minute of the day?
它根本不动
It won't budge.
等等  我觉得我找到了紧急按钮
Oh, wait, I think I found the emergency button.
不不  好吧
No, no! Okay!
杰  我已经努力不发慌了
Jay, I'm trying not to panic.
后退  我要拿一块紧急安全石
Stand back -- I'm gonna throw
砸穿这块玻璃了
one of these emergency rocks through the glass!
好烫
That's hot!
我在给前台发短信
I'm texting the front desk.
听着  菲尔  我做不到
Listen, Phil, I can't do this.
你要离开我了吗
You're leaving me here?!
不  我不能忍受你在这个俱乐部
No, I can't have you at this club!
这是我的地盘  见鬼
This is my place, damn it.
不
No!
对不起  菲尔
I'm sorry, Phil.
你不能另找一个俱乐部吗
Can't you find another club?
看看我的生活
I mean, look at my life.
我建好了自己的房子
I mean, I built my house,
还没等我住进去  我就结婚了
and before I even lived in it, I got married.
是挺棒的
And that's fantastic.
然后我有了自己的书房
And then I have my study,
在那我可以关上门喝一杯苏格兰威士忌
where I can close the door and have a glass of Scotch.
而现在那是乔的房间  也挺好的
And now it's Joe's room, and that's fantastic.
但这里是我仅剩的唯一的
But this is the only place I have left
不用和家人分享的空间
that I don't have to share with my family.
我不想当打断你的白痴  但你发出信息了吗
I don't want to be that guy, but did you send that text yet?
唯一我觉得特别的地方
The one place I feel special --
他们喊我王牌或者杰哥或者普里契
they call me "Ace" and "Jay Boy" and "Pritch."
我在别的地方都没在这里痛快  好吗
I'm not comfortable other places, okay?
而你  你在哪都能融入
But you -- you fit in everywhere.
整个世界都是你的俱乐部
The whole world is your club!
但我只有这个地方
But I have this place!
你懂了吧
You get that, right?
维护人员一分钟后就到了
Maintenance arrived one minute later
用海鲜吧里的冰块把他包了起来
and packed him in ice from the seafood bar,
然后他就完好如初了
and he was as good as new.
你觉得怎么样
How you feeling?
好点了
Better.
杰  我在想你刚刚说的话
Jay, I was thinking about what you said before.
如此真诚  敏感
It was so honest and sensitive.
和脆弱
And vulnerable.
停
Hey.
这件事天知地知你知我知
No one needs to know about that.
不管怎样  这是你的俱乐部
Anyway, this is your club.
我退出吧
I'm -- I'm dropping out.
不  你和我一样理应享受这一切
Well, you deserve it just as much as I do.
没事的
It's fine.
我不能让你放弃这一切
I can't let you give all this up.
拜托  俱乐部里有
For God's sake, there's the club chair
胖子阿巴寇坐着焦急地等待裁决的椅子
Fatty Arbuckle anxiously awaited his verdict.
阿巴寇是好莱坞默片时代喜剧明星  被指控强奸致人死亡
审判三年后无罪释放
杰  我是真心的
Jay, I mean it.
好吧  至少让我送你些什么作为补偿
Well, at least let me give you something in return.
你说吧
You name it.
真的吗
Really?
-对  -那么
- Yeah. - Well...
我不喜欢你现在超级开心的样子
I don't like how happy you look right now.
这才是活着  不是吗
This is living, huh?
我们得在这待多久
How long do we have this thing for?
只有三个小时
Only three hours.
你看到标志了吗
You saw the sign.
每一跳都有价值
Every bounce counts!
太棒了
Yes!
跳起来  跳啊
Get you some! Get it!
我和弗拉德分手的那些事还令我心有余悸
The way things ended with me and Vlad, it always haunted me.
小卡没说错
Cam wasn't wrong about this.
我们买了全票
We paid for the whole seat,
但只看懂了它的边角
but we're only using the edge of it.
你知道吗  我只欠你这么多
You know, I only owe you so much.
我对你的补偿也是有限的
You don't get an unlimited number of these.
泰咪  你绝不会相信谁在这里
Tammy, you are never gonna believe who's here.
-谁  -弗拉德
- Who? - Vlad.
我的天  在哪
Oh, my God, where?
在那里
Out there.
我觉得我得早点溜了
I think might duck out early.
他在那  他就是弗拉德
There he is. That's Vlad.
太幸运了
Lucky!
弗拉德  弗拉德  弗拉德
Vlad! Vlad! Vlad! Vlad! Vlad!